PERFECT CROWN
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED SAFELY
PERFECT CROWN
An accident?
What have you heard exactly?
Only that there was a collision.
I need to be there.
Do not just stand there.
Prepare to leave at once!
Yes, Your Majesty.
THE ROYAL SEOUL HOSPITAL
How did this happen?
What about His Majesty?
Was there an attack on His Majesty's life?
Say something!
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
His scans reveal no fractures or internal injuries.
Just some minor bruising.
:cue
And the Grand Prince?
I heard he was at the scene as well.
Is he all right?
He is in surgery.
It appears his left shoulder bore much of the impact.
It seems he has done everything in his power to stop the car.
Prime Minister Min.
May I have a word?
Photos of the accident have spread on social media.
Her conspicuous vehicle didn't help.
How is Ms. Seong doing?
She's still unconscious, but the scans have come back clean.
Hmm. Are photos of the escort vehicles also circulating?
No. They were some distance away from the scene,
and we're removing them as they appear.
That should be enough.
Pushing too hard will raise--
What did you just say?
What does Ms. Seong Huiju have to do with any of this?
Are you saying the vehicle involved,
the one His Majesty was in, belongs to that woman?
Your Majesty.
Where are you going?
Must I report such things to you?
The wise decision
would be to not go anywhere.
The people know Ms. Seong's vehicle was involved.
So?
"His Majesty was in that car
and the Grand Prince caused an accident to save him,
racking up countless traffic violations and substantial damage in the process."
If word of this got out,
all of this could be blamed
on the young king.
Prime Minister Min.
I am merely stating that it could lead
to such dire conclusions.
Are you trying to protect that maiden?
I am trying to protect the Crown.
OPERATING CENTER
LEE ♪ IN RECOVERY
The surgery went well.
The anesthesia has just worn off,
so he should be able to go up to his room in about an hour.
What about any lasting effects?
I heard it can be difficult to use your arm after shoulder surgery.
The surgery wasn't due to a fracture or a chronic condition,
so that is unlikely.
- No need to worry. - Thank you.
- Thank you, Doctor. - Thank you.
Thank goodness.
- That's a relief. - Yes.
Let's increase security on the floor Ms. Seong is on.
- Send people from our office. - Yes, sir.
Let me know as soon as she wakes up.
Yes, sir. :cue
SEONG HUIJU
Ms. Seong.
Your Majesty?
Are you awake?
Your Majesty! Are you all right?
Is anything broken?
I am sorry.
This all happened because I insisted on a drive.
Not at all.
Your Majesty and I are both fine.
Wait, His Royal Highness.
Where is the Grand Prince? Is he here as well?
Do not worry.
Uncle did not faint.
He even went into the operating room without crying.
The operating room?
He's having surgery?
Would you like some water?
Is the surgery over?
Are you okay?
I mean, what were you thinking, jumping in there?
Are you insane?
Ms. Seong, His Royal Highness has just woken up from the anesthesia…
- You can't just-- - Hold on.
You even hurt your face?
When that's all you have going for you?
Oh, no.
How are you doing?
You were unconscious.
I'm perfectly fine.
Come here.
I'm hurting.
Anywhere else?
I'm fine.
Don't ever jump in like that again.
I need to you stay in one piece so you can have my back.
You were lucky this time.
Imagine if your life was in danger…
You think it would end with just a few eggs?
Then stop putting me in that position. :cue
I can't promise you that.
Then I can't either.
You make it seem like you're madly in love with me.
This is what should be making the headlines.
Babe, you sure this is right?
Yeah, you're almost there.
Okay.
Now put one hand on your chest. Namaste.
What? Nama-what-now?
Namaste.
Right. Nama…
FATHER
- Babe, Father's calling. - What?
Now? Why?
- Does he know you're not at work? - Darn it.
It's not even 8:00 yet.
That's true. Did you do something wrong?
No, I didn't.
Hello, Father.
What? Seong Huiju did?
What in the… Babe, turn the TV on.
Yes.
Last night, a traffic accident occurred on an outlying road in Gyeonggi Province.
- A speeding sports car - Yes, just a moment.
collided with a vehicle in the adjacent lane.
The driver of the sports car was identified as CEO Seong Huiju
of Castle Beauty, sparking further controversy.
It is being reported that Ms. Seong's vehicle
was traveling 50 km/h over the speed limit…
- What do we do? - Father, we'll come to you now.
- The police are still investigating… - All right.
You can't come in here.
Seriously? Don't you remember me from last time?
I'm her assistant at Castle Beauty.
You can't. Please step back.
This is driving me insane.
Then what about him?
Come on! Why do you only ever stop me?
Ms. Seong!
Ms. Do, come here.
She's with me.
Those jerks are the worst.
Unbelievable.
Why do they keep…
I told you I'm fine.
Nothing to worry about.
I'm totally fine.
You'll fix this, right?
LIVE 3-MIN CHART
This was all part of the plan, right?
The chairman is freaking out. He wants you as soon as you're discharged.
He knows I was injured?
Of course…
he does.
And still, not a single word?
Not from Father, or even Seong Taeju?
I mean, how did you even end up in that accident?
- Did you drink and drive? - No, I didn't.
I swear I didn't.
Then were you just speeding for the thrill of it?
You think I'm some kind of lunatic?
Just randomly speeding for the thrill of it?
The car just took off.
The brakes and all weren't working.
What in the world…
Then I'll first prepare a press release with the dashcam footage.
- You can't. - Why not?
You just can't.
His Majesty was with me.
His Majesty?
As in His Majesty the King?
The investigation won't be public.
Damn it.
It just never ends!
Let's reconsider this.
- Reconsider what? - This marriage.
Can't you just call it off?
You're seriously bringing that up now? :cue
There has been nothing but trouble since Prince I-AN entered your life.
Egged at your own door over a little scandal.
One wrong turn in the palace made you an arsonist.
And this time, you nearly died.
Grand Prince I-AN was the one who saved me.
Wait, he was the one who saved you?
Why are you two so caught up in this?
What do you mean?
I mean, why are you two overdoing it?
You'll be divorced in three years anyway.
"Divorced"?
Jeongwoo.
Where did you pop out from?
Is your job fun?
Pardon?
Working at the palace.
Oh, the palace?
Well…
Why? Are you looking to work there too?
Wow.
When Ms. Seong moves into the palace…
I'll be following her.
So charismatic.
You said it was genuine.
Was it all a lie?
I wouldn't go so far as to call it a lie…
Seong Huiju.
It's like a marriage of convenience.
A simple exchange of services.
You know plenty of people like that.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
That's completely different.
How so?
Don't you know how dangerous the palace can be?
- Even this accident-- - I'm fine.
You think I proposed without knowing that?
You proposed to him?
Yeah. I was rejected about three times.
Listen.
I have everything but status.
I have the money, talent, and ambition,
but status is the one thing I don't have.
If I just had that…
I mean, why can't I have that too?
Is that all?
The reason you want to marry him.
Is status all there is to it?
What else could there be?
Then do it with me.
Do what?
Just marry me instead.
That will not do.
The Grand Prince, who had surgery, is returning to the palace.
Then surely, the King should as well.
But, Your Majesty…
If the king remains out of sight,
the people will come to think they do not need one.
Do you not agree?
I agree.
Your Royal Highness, I've been discharged…
Huh?
Has he already been discharged? :cue
Your Royal Highness, Prime Minister Min has arrived.
Show him in.
Your Royal Highness.
You are all dismissed.
I mean,
he should at least tell me if he's been discharged.
Not a great sign for married life.
He didn't say anything at the hospital?
When?
The last time I saw him was early this morning.
What?
But he was standing outside your room earlier.
My room? When?
When Prime Minister Min stopped by.
Then do it with me.
Just marry me instead.
Huh?
So what you're saying is
Ms. Seong was kicked out by His Royal Highness?
Well, I mean, it was more like…
He asked that you return home.
That's the same thing!
PRINCE
Is he kidding me right now?
Your Ladyship! Wait, Your Ladyship.
It's fine.
The master of the house has already spoken.
It's not that.
The hopae.
He would like it returned.
JUNIOR ALUM
Is that all?
The reason you want to marry him.
Is status all there is to it?
What else could there be?
Then do it with me.
Just marry me instead. :cue
Say it to my face.
Whatever it is.
It is a relief that I will never have to teach you.
No matter how great a teacher may be,
there are things that simply cannot be taught.
Pardon?
Your Royal Highness, Ms. Seong Huiju has arrived.
Are you cleared to be out already?
That's your concern?
Why did you kick me out?
Because of the Queen Mother?
Or…
because of Jeongwoo?
What about him?
Didn't you overhear something?
What?
Never mind.
Then why did you kick me out?
I need to know what's going on before I play along or not.
Someone messed with your car.
That is what caused the accident.
Who?
It's being investigated.
We will catch them.
And so,
I'm changing the plan.
Let's…
call off this marriage.
What… What was that?
Call what off now?
The marriage.
But why?
Did Queen Mother tell you to do that?
Because of the accident?
That was because His Majesty was relentless.
And you said someone messed with my car.
That makes me a victim too.
Exactly.
That's why we must call it off.
If I married someone like you
who breaks every rule and has enemies at every turn…
the Crown is bound to fall.
Father, this is a serious accident. :cue
See here.
God, she's even driving on the other side of the road.
If you ask me, at best, she's drunk.
At worst, it's hard drugs. Nowadays, there's this…
Right.
I mean, she's always been desperate for attention.
Now that she's dating Prince I-AN, she's become a total hot tomato.
- And… - Potato.
It's "hot potato." Like a freshly baked hot potato.
Oh, right. Potato.
So, now…
Babe, does that matter?
Tomato. Potato. Same difference.
Sometimes, you can be…
Anyway, Father, this is totally a huge, glaring owner-related risk.
You saw how the stock had shot up over the last few days
and just took a nosedive, didn't you?
At this rate, Castle Beauty will just…
So what?
You want to take over Beauty?
Is that any way to speak to your brother?
What is it?
Let's make this quick. I'm busy.
Explain yourself.
What is there to explain?
It's just as you see.
Can you handle the consequences?
We'll issue a press release soon.
Neither alcohol
nor drugs were involved.
I heard they moved all your things
out of his house today.
Did you have me followed?
Explain yourself first!
It's just a lovers' spat.
Satisfied?
You call yourself a businesswoman,
yet you don't even realize you're being used.
The Grand Prince has used you for all you're worth.
He acted like he was above status, as if he had no ambition for the throne.
Now that he has everything…
he's tossing you out.
So what?
What's the issue?
Two can play that game.
Do you know how much our stock has jumped at the news
of Castle Group's Seong Huiju marrying into the royal family?
Hey, kid. It all tanked today.
It will bounce right back after the press release, damn it.
They're even asking if the "Castle" name was part of some grand plan.
Haven't you seen the news?
Did it ever cross your mind that it'll put a bigger target on our backs?
So we take a few hits!
A few hits won't kill you.
And even if it did, what of it?
We all end up dead anyway.
What, do you plan to live forever?
Next time, just text me instead.
If you want to yell that badly, then feel free to call.
- Sit down. - I have plans.
Seong Huiju!
It's me.
I need you to look into something for me.
Find out who last worked on my car.
Dig up everything you possibly can on them. :cue
A grand prince of this nation can't…
break an engagement.
Technically, there's nothing to break. We were never engaged.
Are you kidding?
After all that talk about getting married and living together?
We never lived together.
- I was at the palace, and she was-- - Listen.
Even if you killed someone, I would take your side.
But this is not cool. It's--
Why would you side with a murderer?
You must've had your reasons.
So, why did you break it off?
- I didn't "break"-- - Seriously? Come on.
That's not what I'm asking.
Why did you break it off?
To keep her alive.
Mother, should we pick up fried chicken on the way to the palace?
Fried chicken?
Hwan texted and said he wanted some.
He's always making me do stuff like this.
Shall we, then?
Yes, Mother.
Mother!
Mother, should we pick up fried chicken on the way to the palace?
Shall we, then?
Mother…
There wasn't a doubt in my mind.
It was a moment I'd regretted countless times.
That's what changed my mind.
It was just an accident.
It wasn't even your fault, so why?
It was my fault.
Signs of deliberate tampering
were found in the accident vehicle.
We'll need to investigate further to determine if they were targeting
His Majesty or Ms. Seong.
However, do not concern yourself too much. :cue
I will do everything in my power to protect
His Majesty, Your Royal Highness,
and the Crown.
In turn,
I'd like to ask you
to protect Ms. Seong Huiju.
Please cast her far away from the palace.
I sincerely implore you, Your Royal Highness.
That is why
I must step aside.
Your Royal Highness.
Thus,
I want to do something.
Pardon?
A parting gift.
For her.
The Inner Court Banquet guest list,
proposed by the Royal Secretariat.
PALACE EVENT HOSTED FOR LADIES OF THE INNER COURT
TRADITIONALLY HELD SINCE THE JOSEON DYNASTY
Remove the scandal-ridden figures.
No new money either.
The merits of these two are comparable.
Bring me the details of their families.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your standards rise every year.
The more exclusive the guest list,
the deeper the despair of the uninvited.
And with it comes the greater delight of those invited.
INNER COURT BANQUET GUEST LIST
Another gathering of the usual suspects this year.
All nobility.
The competition is fiercer every year.
It does offer many benefits.
That is true.
But if they managed to secure an invite,
they must already possess plenty of money and land.
That's precisely why they're willing to die for royal prestige.
It's the only thing their money can't buy.
Ma'am.
I had to jump through some pretty high hoops to secure
this Inner Court Banquet guest list.
A lot of familiar faces, right?
A gathering of female business leaders in their thirties…
Still just 20 of them, right?
Not even enough for a soccer match.
But, ma'am, you said so yourself.
"One absolute is worth more than a hundred maybes."
These are 20 absolutes.
All backed by the Crown, no less!
You once called this the most luxurious marketing strategy…
So what's your point?
Moving on.
Since you have ties with the palace and all, we thought
one of the guests could be a new face of our luxury line.
Yes, so we…
Just a moment. Oh.
Hello.
MS. SEONG HUIJU, YOU ARE CORDIALLY INVITED TO THE INNER COURT BANQUET
Me?
Yes, Ms. Seong.
The Inner Court Banquet is a very important annual event.
Of course, I'm aware of the Inner Court Banquet.
But I thought only noblewomen were invited to this.
What? No such criterion exists…
It certainly doesn't,
but that's how it's been done.
For 600 years, without a single exception.
The thing about change is that it happens gradually…
So? How? Why?
Why have I suddenly been invited?
Yes, well, you've experienced some hardships recently,
and the press release about your breakup is about to go out.
So to make it clear the palace wasn't responsible for your breakup…
You want to stage a performance for the public? :cue
Yes, you see,
the dress codes for the two parts are different.
It's customary to wear a dangui for the reception.
The Queen Mother will wear white, so it's best to avoid that color.
No thanks.
To what exactly? The dangui?
The Inner Court Banquet.
Ms. Seong.
Why?
The Inner Court Banquet? You don't want to attend?
Silly me, how did I forget to mention this?
Attending it once will lead to many more royal invitations.
Even royal patronage for your overseas business.
Okay. Above all else,
this will confirm that you two didn't end things badly,
and that you remain on good terms with the Crown.
We can pivot to an "it's all cool" narrative--
- That would be excellent. - Mm-hmm.
You've always wanted an invite.
That was before marriage was on the table.
No thanks.
But still, His Royal Highness personally…
No…
thank…
you.
What?
So? You just left?
What choice did I have? She was about to murder me in broad daylight.
I heard you moved Seong Huiju out of your private residence.
What are you playing at?
I am protecting her.
Her ties to the Crown
have only led her to misfortune.
Then,
ensure she no longer has any ties to the Crown.
That is my intention.
I will not pursue
marriage with Seong Huiju.
In turn,
I ask that you invite her to the Inner Court Banquet.
I do not wish to see her suffer
because of our parting.
Summon her to the palace.
Ms. Seong Huiju?
You want me to?
I shall persuade her myself.
No thanks.
No, thank you.
Who is he to summon me?
Is the fried chicken here?
What? You ordered fried chicken again?
You open it.
Mmm.
People have nothing on fried chicken, right?
It shows up right on time when you call them.
You never get sick of it.
Always so reliable.
- Wait… - What?
Are you upset you got dumped?
Why would you say that when I'm enjoying fried chicken?
I'm done.
Oh, I mean…
Why are you so upset?
It was all pretend.
That's exactly why.
Relationships end when one side loses interest,
whether the other likes it or not.
But that's not what this was.
This was strictly a contract.
Father was right.
I'm a businesswoman. I should've known better than to trust a stranger.
I should've drawn up a contract. :cue
Ms. Seong, the invite--
No thanks.
Ms. Seong.
-  You're really not going? - No, thank you!
Is she dumb?
Just give up already.
She doesn't want anything to do with you.
Choi Hyeon.
I mean, I can't blame her.
You dumped her and now you're acting so uncool.
Hey, Ms. Seong.
I went to the repair shop and secured
the résumé of the bastard who tampered with your car and fled.
They ran a search with his photo,
but he doesn't seem to have any priors.
He must've bought something there at least once.
What?
There's a convenience store in front of the shop.
Oh, right.
Scour their CCTV footage.
I want his purchase history.
Say it to my face.
Whatever it is.
Are you afraid to go to the banquet?
I will prepare everything you need.
From the clothes
to the etiquette lessons.
Why?
I break every rule and have enemies at every turn.
- So why would I go there? - Seong Huiju.
Then provide me with a convincing reason.
You risked your life to save me, just to break off the engagement.
And now you're inviting me to the Inner Court Banquet?
A split personality?
I am trying to protect you!
We're not even married…
and you've been attacked multiple times.
And once the breakup news breaks,
it'll only get worse.
So what?
"Social ascent is dangerous. Be content with an invite to the banquet."
- Is that it? - Just stay out of harm's way.
Is that so difficult?
Coward.
What?
- What are you… - You like cats.
Try protecting them.
I'm going to attack them.
What the hell are you doing?
This is how you protect someone.
You go on the offensive.
You fight back.
You never learned to bend.
You only know how to bend. That's why you lose to people beneath you.
I asked you for status,
not a cozy cradle to hide from the world.
Do not bend to their will. :cue
Do not back away
and do not compromise.
That's how you and I both
get what we want.
She is one scary lady.
I know all's fair in love and war,
but isn't this taking it too far?
Is a "safe exit" an option here?
I told you I hurt myself.
Even so, how could she let your precious body be injured?
She has crossed the line.
I told you she didn't.
She never released the arrow.
What?
She never crossed the line.
My eyes are fried.
He must've been super diligent.
Never going to the convenience store across the street.
My thoughts exactly.
Wait.
I think this is him.
Take a look at this.
- It's him, right? -  Yeah, it is.
Castle Pay!
- Yeah, he used Castle Pay! - He did.
Good job!
Hold on.
But the CEO of Castle Card is Senior Managing Director Seong, isn't it?
Let me get this straight.
You need help from your dear brother.
Yes.
I mean, sure.
I could do that for you, but--
Who is he anyway?
He's trying to kill me.
This kid…
Do you take me for a sucker?
Are you serious?
So show me what you can do.
I want some vigilante justice.
This kid…
Who is this guy anyway?
Then do it with me.
Just marry me instead.
Why would I marry you?
Why not?
It's not like you have feelings
for either of us.
You have a five-year term.
It doesn't matter if I mess up or divorce him.
He'll be a royal for life.
But you're different.
You should serve another term.
Pull yourself together. :cue
Is it weighing on your mind?
I heard from Aide Choi.
That there was an argument at your private residence.
Choi Hyeon…
He can be quite the chatterbox.
Just let her win if you can.
She is already under the cutting scrutiny
of the court of public opinion.
PRINCE
Hello.
The invitation has already been sent.
So you cannot decline.
It's for your sake.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I never meant to hurt you.
Or the cat.
I know.
I'm sorry too.
For not keeping my promise.
As long as you know.
CASTLE BEAUTY
I heard you will be attending.
Yes, well, he just insisted it would be in my best interest.
There's one thing you should be aware of.
- Just a moment. - Sure.
- Please continue. - All right.
All the other invited guests hold official rank.
In the royal court, rank defines one's place in the hierarchy.
- Hierarchy? - Yes. Uh…
I'm sure you noticed after attending a few royal events.
When you're with someone of a higher rank,
you must walk behind them. That's the custom.
I'll keep that in mind.
Thank you.
And there's this.
Here.
The first half is a smaller gathering where the Queen Mother
and the guests mingle.
The second half is a ball.
They call it an "after-party,"
but with the guests' partners, Cabinet members, and royal family members
all attending, it's larger in scale than the first part.
I read an article about this while studying abroad.
You wear gowns and dance…
That's correct.
Then what will Ms. Seong's rank be?
Her rank…
Ms. Seong is super accomplished and all,
but she has no official rank.
- What? - Well…
She's neither a public official
nor a noble.
So Ms. Seong will be sitting at the very back of the room
and will always be last in line.
:cue
I would be in front of the line if I were married, right?
"The attendees receive honorary decorations
from the royal family and gain the privilege
of accompanying the court when it hosts diplomatic events,
starting with the year they are invited."
It is a relief that I will never have to teach you.
As if she'd ever grant me such privileges.
PRINCE
Hello?
Right now?
What's this about?
Why not?
This will be the last time.
Where did you ever find the nerve to wear that cheollik?
Was that just a stylistic choice?
I'm doing all this for your sake…
What are you doing?
Don't mind me. Just practicing.
- Practicing what? - Walking according to rank.
I'll definitely end up walking ahead that day if I don't practice now.
Because I'm always a trendsetter, leading the way.
- A word, please! - Please look over here!
- Over here! - Give us a pose!
I trust all the preparations are in order?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Bye.
Wait.
"Leading the way."
How do you do it?
I just never learned.
I was always the one following behind.
You just need to walk by my side.
I'll teach you.
Now that Dano, when yang energy is said to be at its peak, has passed,
the Inner Court Banquet has finally commenced.
It's a gathering of 20 young women
centered around the Queen Mother, the head of the Inner Court.
This year's guest list includes Seong Huiju, CEO of Castle Beauty,
drawing significant attention.
-  Babe! - You scared me.
Babe.
I found the punk who rigged her car.
You did?
Yeah, but…
But?
He's dead.
- What? - He died.
Yesterday. :cue
JUNIOR 4TH RANK, SENIOR 4TH RANK
JUNIOR 5TH RANK
JUNIOR 6TH RANK
SEONG HUIJU, COMMONER
For all her much-touted success abroad,
she was never invited.
It seems being the Grand Prince's woman
outweighs any barrier of status.
If she successfully marries him, she will be royalty,
so they must be keeping up appearances.
Even so,
is she not someone who caused a public scandal?
If she had been a guest last year,
at least they could have used her achievements as an excuse.
The royal family is such a joke these days.
- Your Majesty. - Your Majesty.
SEONG HUIJU, COMMONER
Were you speaking ill of someone who is not even here?
Pardon?
I should have come later.
Considering you saw fit
to drag the royal family into your gossip.
Ms. Seong, over here!
- Ms. Seong, over here! - Please look here!
Your Majesty.
I am Huiju of the Seong Family.
-  Ms. Seong. -  Ms. Seong!
How does it feel to be back at the palace since going public?
What was the palace's stance on the accident?
Is there a reason why you arrived after Her Majesty?
-  Please give us a comment! -  Please!
- We await your response. - Give us a comment.
Unfortunately, I still do not know my way around the palace.
I ended up losing my way for a moment.
Please forgive me,
Your Majesty.
I was told the Royal Secretariat provided you with guidance.
Did you avoid wearing a dangui for some particular reason?
Ah!
I was led to believe that custom was not mandatory.
Is it not to your liking?
How could it not be?
-  Would you care to respond? -  Ms. Seong, over here.
The snacks Your Majesty sent for Children's Day
brought great joy to all the patients in the pediatric ward.
I am more than happy to help in any way I can.
Do not hesitate to let me know.
I heard Your Majesty enjoyed my performances.
If Your Majesty could attend the next one, I would be greatly honored…
Perhaps the summer is to thank,
but do you not find the palace grounds even more beautiful?
Pardon?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let us walk a bit longer.
When the flowers are in bloom, appreciating them is one's duty.
- Yes, Your Majesty. - Yes, Your Majesty.
Please teach me.
Now that I am by your side.
:cue
Do not bend to their will.
Do not step back
and do not compromise.
I shall fight with all that I have.
Just as you do.
PERFECT CROWN
From when you were just acquaintances to now,
what would you say is the biggest change?
Being overprotective?
That's a bit too naive, no?
A businesswoman should know better than to trust people so easily.
There's a spy at my private residence.
Seong Huiju!
Don't you find him to be so impatient?
Your Royal Highness?
Will you give me your hand in marriage?
Did you think I would simply let this stand?
Announce me.
How could I refuse a request from the Queen Mother?
You should only have eyes for me.
As if we were hopelessly in love.
EPILOGUE
Oh!
Wait.
You…
You did well
during the exhibition match.
Are you trying to take credit?
"Take credit"?
Do you not grasp the concept of a compliment?
I guess not.
Darn it, you scared me.
Have you been there?
- Yes. - Since when?
Before you started lingering.
Are you close to Seong Huiju?
We're close. We live in the same dorms too.
What is she like?
She's pretty.
Yeah, she is.
Translated by Justin S. Kim
PERFECT CROWN